Guide to the Charles Baptie photograph collection, 1917-1995
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 5: Texaco Stations, 1950-1972
  - Texaco, 1952-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1-43)
    Images of Texaco stations, including pictures; negatives; Fairlington area; Central and 495; Waynewood Fort Hunt Road; Route 7 and Route 81 Winchester; Central and Bell Highway; Annandale East; Fort Ward Tower, Annandale; Central Avenue and Addison Road, SW Washington, D.C.,; Gainesville; Gaithersburg; Kenilworth Avenue Station and Watkins Station; Riggs Road and Ager Road; New Hampshire Avenue and E.W Highway; Ritchie Road and Central Avenue, NE; aerial views; Wilson Boulevard and Edison Street; Bolling Field, Cheverly; EW Highway and Colesvill Road; Brown's Texaco; New York and W. VA, 2nd and Riggs; Ronnie Peppe; Conomingo; Buddy Johnson; New York Avenue Station; prints and negatives; blueprints and maps; Gaithersburg; Gaithersburg South; Germantown; Hamilton; Bill Hawk Texaco; Herndon Route 7; and Herndon Junction.
  - Texaco, 1950-1960 (Box 13, Folder 1-54)
    Images of Texaco stations at Route 50 and Baltimore Highway; Piney Branch and Silver Spring Avenue; New York Avenue Training station; New Hampshire and Kennedy Street, NW; New Hampshire and EW Highway; Mt. Vernon Ridge Road, Glebe Road intersection; Mosby Woods; Wilson Boulevard and Peyton Drive, near Seven Corners; Washington Lane Shopping Center; Takoma Park; Silver Spring Avenue, Piney Branch; Shirlington; Andrews Field, Morningside MD; Mt. Vernon Avenue and Monroe, Alexandria; Morningside; Woodstock; Woodbridge; Marumsco Village and Route 1; Connecticut Avenue and St Station; Dulles; Fairfax Town; Fairfax Drive, Falls Church; aerial view of Park; Fort Hunt Road section; Georgia and Hobart Drive; Georgia Avenue and Old Bladensburg Road; Georgia and Sher; Herndon; Lee Highway and Old Dominion Drive; MacArthur Boulevard; Clarendon area; Fairfax Drive and N. Quincy; Art Harold; aerial views; Plant, Alexandria; 6th and Florida Avenue, NE; 41st at Southern Avenue; Ager Road and Hamilton Street, NW; River Road, Alexandria; S. Wood Street, Alexandria; Annandale; Bethesda area; East Capitol and 64th Shady Grove; aerial view of S. Capitol Street and Lexington Road; S. Capitol Street and M Street; S. Capitol and Nicholas Street; Centreville; Columbia Pike; Station; Alexandria; and Rithie Road and Central Avenue, NE.
  - Texaco, 1960s (Box 41)
    Negative of a Texaco Service Station.
  - Texaco, 1960s-1970s (Box 43)
    Images of Texaco. (negatives)
  - Texaco, 1951 (Box 45)
    Texaco station on Duke Street.
  - Texaco, 1960s-1970s (Box 52)
    Texaco aerial views. (negatives)
  - Texaco, 1960s (Box 53)
    Street and aerial view of an Annandale area Texaco station. (with negatives)
  - Texaco, 1950s-1960s (Box 54)
    Images and negatives of Texaco stations.
- Series 6: Hot Shoppes, 1948-1953
  This series contains negatives of Hot Shoppes Restaurants in the greater Washington, D.C., area. This was a restaurant owned by the Marriott company and the series includes images of food, their Airline service, their kitchens, and the dining rooms of Hot Shoppes.
  - Hot Shoppes, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Food (1 of 2)
  - Hot Shoppes, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Food (2 of 2)
  - Hot Shoppes, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Cakes
  - Hot Shoppes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Airport Airline Service
  - Hot Shoppes, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Pantry House
  - Hot Shoppes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Salt Lake City
  - Hot Shoppes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Meridian Hall
  - Hot Shoppes, 1948, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    J.W. Marriott
  - Hot Shoppes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Virginia
  - Hot Shoppes, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Washington, D.C.
  - Hot Shoppes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Maryland
  - Hot Shoppes, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Kitchens, Etc.
  - Hot Shoppes, 1948-1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Hot Shoppes (1 of 5)
  - Hot Shoppes, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Hot Shoppes (2 of 5)
  - Hot Shoppes, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Hot Shoppes (3 of 5)
  - Hot Shoppes, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Hot Shoppes (4 of 5)
  - Hot Shoppes, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Hot Shoppes (5 of 5)
  - Photo Album, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Photographs of kitchens, possibly Hot Shoppes.
  - Hot Shoppes, undated (Box 30)
    Images of Hot Shoppes can be found within this box.
  - Hot Shoppes, 1950s (Box 41)
    Negatives of Hot Shoppes are in this box.
  - Hot Shoppes, 1950s (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Large format images of kitchens.
- Series 7: D.C. Monuments, 1944-1991
  This series contains photographic prints, negatives, and slides of D.C. monuments. Some of these images are listed in other series as necessary. The monuments include Capitol Hill, the Lincoln Memorial, the Jefferson Memorial, the Washington Monument, the White House, and Mount Vernon, for example.
  - Capitol Hill, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Capitol Hill photographs. (negatives)
  - Jefferson Memorial, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Cherry Blossoms at the Jefferson Memorial. (negatives)
  - Washington Scenes, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Images of the White House, Supreme Court, Taft Bridge, the Potomac River, the Library of Congress, and other Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - WAVES Second Birthday Celebration, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Various Washington, D.C., monuments in regards to the birthday celebration. (negatives)
  - Fireworks, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Fireworks over Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Jefferson Memorial, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Jefferson Memorial.
  - Lincoln Memorial, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Lincoln memorial and Washington Monument.
  - Lincoln Memorial, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - US Capitol, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Photographs of the US Capitol.
  - US Capitol, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Jefferson Memorial, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Photographs of the Jefferson Memorial.
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Photographs of Washington, D.C., monuments taken from the air.
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1940s, 1960s, 1970s (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Photographs and postcards of Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Photographs of Washington, D.C., monuments. (with negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Monuments, 1949, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Photographs of monuments. (with negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fireworks, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Photographs of fireworks over Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Postcards, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Postcards of Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Mount Vernon, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Photographs of Mount Vernon.
  - Woodlawn, 1960, 1975, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Photographs of Mount Vernon and Woodlawn plantation.
  - White House, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    White house interior photographs.
  - White House, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    White House negatives.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1960s (Box 27)
    Various Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1940s-1960s (Box 28)
    Various Washington, D.C., monuments. (negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1980s (Box 30)
    Various Washington, D.C., monuments, many aerial views.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1940s (Box 31)
    Image of the Washington Monument.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1960s (Box 33)
    Images of the Washington, D.C., monuments and hotels.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1950, 1955 (Box 34)
    Aerial views of Washington, D.C., monuments. (negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1958 (Box 35)
    Fireworks over Washington, D.C. (with negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1970s (Box 36)
    Aerial views of Washington, D.C., along with pictures of Washington, D.C., monuments, including Mount Vernon. (with negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1940s (Box 39)
    Images of Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1955 (Box 41)
    Images of the White House as well as area hotels. (with negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1953-1964 (Box 42)
    Images of Washington, D.C., monuments through various years. Includes several of the areas famous houses.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, undated (Box 44)
    Images of Mount Vernon.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1940s (Box 46)
    Images of Washington, D.C., Circle Road, Washington, D.C., Monuments, and famous houses in the area.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1964-1974 (Box 51)
    Images of the White House and other Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1960s (Box 53)
    Images of various Washington, D.C., monuments, including Gadsby Tavern, St. Clements Church, and Lee Mansion. (negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1966 (Box 58)
    Various Washington, D.C., monuments, including aerial views.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1940s (Box 59)
    Images of the White House, buildings along the mall in Washington, D.C.,, and aerial views of monuments.
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1980s (Box 62)
    Large format photographs of fireworks over Washington, D.C.
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1960s (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Images of Washington, D.C., from the ground and the air, including Georgetown, Mount Vernon, the Pentagon, and the Reflecting Pool.
  - Buildings, 1940s-1960s (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Large format images of the Library of Congress, Lincoln Memorial, Memorial Amphitheater, Supreme Court building, and the White House.
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, 1940s-1970s (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Large format images of Washington, D.C., monuments. (with negatives)
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Aerial views of Washington D.C. with Capital Airlines plane.
  - Washington, D.C., monuments, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Large format images of Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Washington Monument and other sites in Washington, D.C., 1940s-1990 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Large format images the Washington monument and other Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1979 (Box 71)
    Panoramic photograph of Washington, D.C. from the Ellipse by Michael Lawton for Perpetual Federal Savings.
- Series 8: Aerial Photos, 1934-1991
  This series contains aerial photographs and negatives of the D.C. area. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Aerial views include those of Alexandria, Annandale, Texaco service stations, construction sites, Washington, D.C., monuments, Gunston Hall, Sully Plantation, and the Potomac River.
  - Alexandria Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Aerial views of Alexandria
  - Alexandria Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Aerial views of Route 1
  - Washington Scenes, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Aerial views of Washington, D.C.
  - Washington Aerial Views, 1934-1940, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Unidentified, 1980s (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Unidentified aerial views.
  - Besley, Oliver, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Aerial views for Besley, Oliver.
  - Texaco, 1950-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1, 3-5, 8-17, 19-22, 24-26, 37-40, 42)
    Aerial views of Texaco service stations around Washington, D.C.
  - Texaco, 1950-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1-2, 4-9, 11-15, 17-20, 22-26, 28-34, 36-37, 39-42, 44-51, 53-54)
    Aerial views of Texaco service stations around Washington, D.C..
  - National Memorial Park, 1961-1964 (Box 14, Folder 4, 11, 15)
    Aerial views of the National Memorial Park.
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Aerial views of a construction site.
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Construction site, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Photographs of aerial views.
  - Aerials, 1960s, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Aerials, 1960s, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Air views of FGE, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Air view, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Air view of Columbia Pike area.
  - Aerial views, 1958, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Photographs of aerial views of the Washington, D.C., area and Annandale.
  - Aerial views of Washington, D.C., monuments, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Negatives of three Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Aerial views of Washington, D.C., monuments, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 28)
    Aerial views of houses, embassies, restaurants, hotels, and streets around Washington, D.C. (negatives)
  - Aerial Views, 1980s (Box 30)
    Aerial views of Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 31)
    Aerial Washington, D.C., views. (negatives)
  - Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 33)
    Aerial views of Sully Plantation and an unknown vacation resort. (negatives)
  - Aerial Views, 1993, 1960s (Box 34)
    Aerial prints of Fairfax Hills and aerial views of Washington, D.C., from helicopter.
  - Aerial Views, 1950s (Box 35)
    Aerial view of a storm cloud and of Washington, D.C..
  - Aerial Views, 1980s (Box 36)
    Aerial images of Gunston Hall, Fairfax, Annandale, Washington, D.C., and Pittsburgh.
  - Aerial Views, 1968-1991 (Box 37)
    Aerial views (slides) of aircraft and hot air balloons, Washington, D.C., Mount Vernon, and Gunston Hall.
  - Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 38)
    Aerial images of Gunston Hall.
  - Aerial Views, 1960s, 1970s (Box 39)
    City aerial views.
  - Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 40)
    aerial images within the malaria testing and prevention series.
  - Aerial Views, 1950s-1960s (Box 41)
    Aerial photos.
  - Aerial Views, 1960-1962 (Box 42)
    Aerial views of the area, including Bailey's Crossroads.
  - Aerial Views, 1980s (Box 44)
    Air views of Annandale, VA.
  - Aerial Views, undated (Box 46)
    Aerial shots of a PTS in Arlington and of Carvan.
  - Aerial Views, 1951-1952 (Box 47)
    Aerial views of Glebe and Arlington, St. Stephens school, and Fairfax Hills.
  - Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 48)
    Aerial views.
  - Aerial Views, 1964-1974 (Box 51)
  - Aerial Views, 1960s-1970s (Box 52)
    Texaco aerial views.
  - Aerial Views, 1960s (Box 53)
    Air view of Annandale, Butterfly Hill, and a Texaco station in the Annandale area.
  - Aerial Views, 1980s (Box 55)
    Air views of a construction site.
  - Aerial Views, 1966 (Box 58)
    Aerial views of the Washington, D.C., area.
  - Aerial views, 1970s (Box 62)
    Aerial views of a hospital, church, the Pentagon, and a map.
  - Aerials, 1960s (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Aerial views of Washington D.C., Alexandria, Mount Vernon, Potomac River, and the Pentagon.
  - Aerial photos, 1950-1976 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Large format prints of aerial photos.
  - Washington, D.C., Monuments, 1979 (Box 71)
    Aerial panoramic photograph of Washington, D.C. from the Ellipse by Michael Lawton for Perpetual Federal Savings.
- Series 9: Nature, 1917-1988
  This series contains photographs, negatives and slides of nature, including gardens, fireworks, sunsets, clouds, bodies of water, landscapes, and cemeteries. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary.
  - Butterfly Hill, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Negatives of butterflies and flowers at Butterfly Hill.
  - Clouds and Sunset at Wakefield, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Images of clouds and the sunset at Wakefield. (negatives)
  - Dumfries, VA, 1917-1937, 1958, 1981-1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Images of Dumfries, VA natural scenes.
  - Fireworks, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Images of fireworks.
  - Harpers Ferry, WV, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Images of Harpers Ferry, WV. (negatives)
  - Jefferson Memorial [Cherry Blossoms], 1956 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Images of cherry Blossoms at the Jefferson Memorial. (negatives)
  - Little River Turnpike, 1949, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Images of Little River Turnpike.
  - Sunset on the Potomac, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Images of a sunset on the Potomac. (negatives)
  - Riggs Bank, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Images of nature at Riggs Bank. (negatives)
  - US Route 1, Near Fort Belvoir, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Images of nature along US Route 1 near Fort Belvoir. (negatives)
  - Views along Route 40, 1950s-1960s (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Images of nature along Route 40. (negatives)
  - Cemetery Series, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Scenes of nature in a cemetery. (negatives)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Scenes of miscellaneous nature.
  - American Association of Nurserymen, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 2, 3)
    Natural photos for the American Association of Nurserymen. (negatives)
  - American Weekly, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Photos of natural and zoo scenes for American Weekly. (negatives)
  - Geophysical Labs, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Natural scenes around Geophysical Labs. (negatives)
  - National Memorial Park, 1953-1967 (Box 14, Folder 1-17)
    Natural scenes at National Memorial Park.
  - River, Fishing, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Fishing on a river
  - Park Plans, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Park plans
  - Nature, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Photographs of mountains, a glacier, water, and a cave.
  - Nature, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Photographs of a graveyard.
  - Nature, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Negatives of birds and mushrooms.
  - Nature, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Photographs of bees and flowers and trees.
  - Flowers, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Slides of flowers.
  - Natural Bridge, 1960s-1970s (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Negatives of natural bridge.
  - Nature, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    Nature scenes surrounding Little Theatre, DAR, Blair house, Statler hotel, Sand Meridian, Shrine of Immaculate Conception, Harvey Rest, Holiday Inn, Kenmore's House, or Uranium ore sample. (with negatives)
  - Nature, 1950s-1960s (Box 26)
    Natural scenes of Riverside Garden, Waynewood, Woodlawn, and Kurty. (negatives)
  - Nature, 1960s (Box 29)
    Natural scenes in Ecuador and Honduras dealing with the malaria prevention series.
  - Nature, 1930s, 1950s, 1970s (Box 30)
    Images of a river, Niagara Falls, and fireworks.
  - Nature, 1960s (Box 31)
    Scenic mountain views, cattle, flowers, and scenes in Ecuador.
  - Nature, 1970s (Box 33)
    Natural images from Sully Plantation, desert scenes, St. Petersburg, and a vacation resort.
  - Nature, 1950s (Box 35)
    Images of a beach vacation, fishing, and a storm cloud.
  - Nature, 1967, 1980s (Box 36)
    Images of Belvedere beach, Africa, and Gunston Hall.
  - Nature, 1981, 1985, 1988 (Box 37)
    Scenic images of a vacation, hot air balloons, Mount Vernon, and Gunston Hall. (slides)
  - Nature, 1990, 1970s (Box 38)
    Photos of Great Falls, Fairfax Hills, Nepal, and butterflies on flowers. (with negatives)
  - Nature, 1960s (Box 39)
    Images from Ecuador and of caves.
  - Nature, 1960s (Box 40)
    Scenic images in regards to the malaria testing and prevention series.
  - Nature, 1952 (Box 41)
    Natural scenes of snow on Butterfly Hill.
  - Nature, 1953-1962 (Box 42)
    Images of the Potomac River.
  - Nature, 1960s, 1970s (Box 44)
    Images of nature from vacation or foreign travel photos, Ecuador, Guatemala, the malaria prevention series, and of butterflies.
  - Nature, 1960s (Box 50)
    Malaria prevention and testing campaign in Ecuador.
  - Nature, 1953, 1961, 1964 (Box 53)
    Images of a flood in Accotink and Fairfax Falls. Also, images of a covered bridge in Vermont; Fairfax Hills; and Butterfly Hill.
  - Nature, undated (Box 62)
    Images of a lake.
  - Nature, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Great Falls of the Potomac: Close up view of the Great Falls, labeled on back as largest falls in the East outside of Niagara.
  - Scenic Pictures (1 of 2), 1950s (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Large format scenic pictures.
  - Scenic Pictures (2 of 2), 1950s (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Series 10: Maps and Building Plans, 1941-1973
  This series contains photographs and negatives of various maps and building plans. This includes blueprints and architectural designs too. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Specific topics include St. Agnes School, Baltimore, Texaco, Hazelton labs, Woodbridge Toll Center, and Fairfax Hills.
  - Baltimore, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Map or plans of Baltimore.
  - Washington D.C., Highway Improvement Program, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Map or plans of Washington D.C., Highway Improvement Program.
  - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Miscellaneous map or plans.
  - St. Agnes School, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Map or plans of St. Agnes School.
  - Churches, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Plans and maps of churches.
  - Houses, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Plans and maps of houses.
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Miscellaneous plans and maps.
  - American Association of Nursery Men, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Plans and maps for the American Association of Nursery Men.
  - Allen Dickey, Architect, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Plans and maps for Allen Dickey, Architect.
  - Hazelton Labs (2 of 6), 1965, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Plans and blueprints from Hazelton Labs.
  - Blueprints/maps, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Texaco maps and blueprints.
  - National Memorial Park, 1961-1964 (Box 14, Folder 1-3, 7, 12-13, 16-17)
    Drawings, plans, and maps of National Memorial Park.
  - Woodbridge Toll Center, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Plans for Woodbridge Toll Center
  - Building plans, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Plans for apartments in Florida, Grasshopper Green School, and Coastal Aviation.
  - Hogate, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Study of Hogate's waterside development.
  - Plans, 1950s (Box 30)
    Apartment plans.
  - Map, undated (Box 38)
    Map and images of Homestead, PA.
  - Plans, undated (Box 39)
    Floor plan of Woodlawn.
  - Plans, 1960s (Box 40)
    Building plans and layouts from the malaria testing and prevention series.
  - Plans, 1941, 1950 (Box 47)
    Plans and maps of Fairfax Hills.
  - Plans, 1964 (Box 49)
    Various plans.
  - Plans, 1952 (Box 53)
    Personality homes plans by Verkerke.
  - Map, undated (Box 54)
    Map of Washington, D.C.,
- Series 11: People, 1944-1976
  This series contains prints and negatives of people in various settings. Some of these photos are listed in other series as necessary. Many photos have unidentified subjects, while others show notable Washingtonians and politicians, athletes, scientists, wedding guests, Presidents, actors, the National Symphony, and military leaders.
  - Cathedral Series, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Pictures of people in the Cathedral series.
  - Cavalier Hotel, 1950s (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Pictures of people at the Cavalier Hotel.
  - Miscellaneous Portraits, 1947, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Pictures of miscellaneous portraits.
  - Cemetery Series, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Pictures of people from the cemetery series. (negatives)
  - Choral Society, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Pictures of people from the choral society.
  - Churches, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Pictures of people from churches. (with negatives)
  - Coffee taster, Food and Drug Department, Department of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Pictures of a coffee taster from the Food and Drug Department, Department of Agriculture. (negatives)
  - Omer Hirst Series, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Pictures of people from the Omer Hirst series. (negatives)
  - Edward Everett Horton, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Pictures of Edward Everett Horton. (negatives)
  - Inauguration Eisenhower, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Pictures of people from President Eisenhower's 1957 inauguration. (negatives)
  - Leighton, Frances, 1960, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Pictures of Frances Leighton. (with negatives)
  - Neil McElroy, Secretary of Defense, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Pictures of Neil McElroy, Secretary of Defense. (negatives)